{"question":"Who is the Ex president of india","options":["Pranav Mukharjee"," Ramnath Kovind","Shri Ravi Shankar","Narendra Modi"],"correctIndex":"1","user_ques":"5","uid":"id1632238257404&u3&q5&t145","_id":"6eQOmr935cZFXVaQ"}
{"question":"Which of the following is not a valid loop","options":["while","do","for","if"],"correctIndex":"4","user_ques":"5","uid":"id1632238257404&u3&q5&t145","_id":"8605nezy6lBQlZrp"}
{"question":"Which of the following is not a valid loop","options":["While","f","f","h"],"correctIndex":"4","user_ques":"2","uid":"id1632858229220&u1&q2&t145","_id":"AbY8Nh13IpKs26h4"}
{"question":"Capital of india?","options":["Haryana","Delhi","Sidhi","Indore"],"correctIndex":"2","user_ques":"4","uid":"id1632877072495&u3&q4&t120","_id":"Ee3MeahKGbLyFzHJ"}
{"question":"Which of the following is not a valid loop","options":["While","for","do while","if"],"correctIndex":"4","user_ques":"4","uid":"id1632877072495&u3&q4&t120","_id":"GY3j6bSxShwkbboK"}
{"question":"Which of the following is not a valid operator","options":["fd",null,null,null],"correctIndex":"3","user_ques":"2","uid":"id1632858229220&u1&q2&t145","_id":"Gft72d7hNEGedvxA"}
{"question":"Osama Bin Laded died in","options":["Pakistan","India","Usa","New Zealand"],"correctIndex":"1","user_ques":"5","uid":"id1632238257404&u3&q5&t145","_id":"InMSFa07KFXWAZxy"}
{"question":"Capital of MP?","options":["Indore","bhopal","sidhi","rewa"],"correctIndex":"2","user_ques":"4","uid":"id1632877072495&u3&q4&t120","_id":"JWg43LfqbjCb4Moy"}
{"question":"JigglyPuff is character of","options":["Doraemon","Pokemon","Kitretsu","Shinchan"],"correctIndex":"2","user_ques":"5","uid":"id1632238257404&u3&q5&t145","_id":"ThaogzwoccEWqNx4"}
{"question":"Gujrat is in","options":["south west","south east","west","north east"],"correctIndex":"3","user_ques":"4","uid":"id1632877072495&u3&q4&t120","_id":"eC7z0pfpo6TqRctp"}
{"question":"Which of the following is not a valid loop","options":["While","f","f","h"],"correctIndex":"2","user_ques":"4","uid":"id1632858283900&u2&q4&t145","_id":"rGTCYChwgH5ysShc"}
{"question":"Corona Virus Origin was in","options":["Pune","Beijing","Wuhan","Hong Kong"],"correctIndex":"3","user_ques":"5","uid":"id1632238257404&u3&q5&t145","_id":"sjPgiSQRmVfh90wq"}
{"question":"Which of the following is not a valid loop","options":["While",null,null,null],"correctIndex":"3","user_ques":"4","uid":"id1632858283900&u2&q4&t145","_id":"vihBsyjcYn0BvbzN"}
{"question":"Which of the following is not a valid operator","options":["While","f","f","h"],"correctIndex":"1","user_ques":"4","uid":"id1632858283900&u2&q4&t145","_id":"w2WKixiIQRLFMNLP"}
{"question":"Which of the following is not a valid loopd","options":["4",null,null,null],"correctIndex":"3","user_ques":"4","uid":"id1632858283900&u2&q4&t145","_id":"wMDL9WzTLMoYMCbO"}
